http://www.pandifootball.net/privacy-notice

PRIVACY NOTICE
Your personal dataPrivacy Notice for members, prospects and suppliers(Last updated: May 25, 2018)Pitstone and Ivinghoe Junior Football Club cares about your privacyPitstone and Ivinghoe Junior Football Club ("PIJFC") is committed to protecting the personal information that you provide to PIJFC, in adherence to Data Protection Legislation (defined below) and best business practice.This Privacy Notice describes PIJFC’s practices in relation to the use of its websites, products and services that it offers. This Privacy Notice sets out how PIJFC uses and protects any personal data that you provide to PIJFC (including personal data provided through its websites).PIJFC maintains the same practices with data that is collected off-line and this notice may be relied upon with respect to those methods of data collection and use.PIJFC may modify or update its Privacy Notice at any time without prior notice. You can check the “Last updated” date above to see when the notice was last changed.How to contact usIf you have any questions regarding your personal data and how PIJFC may use it, including any queries relating to this Privacy Notice, please contact us by emailing secretary@pandifootball.net.It is important that the personal data PIJFC holds about you is accurate and current. Please keep PIJFC informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with PIJFC.Terminology usedPIJFC’s data protection and privacy measures are governed by the (i) the General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (“GDPR”) and any national implementing laws, regulations and secondary legislation, as amended or updated from time to time, in the UK and then (ii) any successor legislation to the GDPR or the Data Protection Act 1998 (“Data Protection Legislation").For the purpose of Data Protection Legislation, where personal data is provided directly to PIJFC through use of its website, email, or other means where PIJFC is determining the way in which that personal data is processed, then PIJFC will be a data controller of such information.Information we collectPersonal data means any data or information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).If you chose to become a member of PIJFC, you are required to complete a Joining Form and resister personal details via the Football Association’s online service - the Whole Game System. When joining, you will be required to provide personal information such as name, email address and telephone number ("Identity Data"). In additional, member age, medical information and emergency contact details will also be recorded. This type of personal information is often known as "sensitive personal data" and will be treated as such.If you are aged 18 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission before you provide any personal information to PIJFC. Without this consent, you are not allowed to provide PIJFC with personal information.When visiting the PIJFC website, information is captured using cookies. To find out more about PIJFC’s use of website cookies, please visit our cookie policy
page.If you fail to provide personal dataWhere PIJFC needs to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract PIJFC has with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, PIJFC may not be able to perform the contract it has or is trying to enter. In this case, PIJFC may have to cancel the services but it will notify you if this is the case at the time.How we use information that we collectPIJFC will only use your personal data when the law allows it to, i.e. if PIJFC has a legal basis for doing so, as outlined in this Privacy Notice or as notified to you at the time in which PIJFC collects your personal data, and for the purposes for which it was collected for, unless PIJFC reasonably considers that it needs to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If PIJFC needs to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, PIJFC will notify you and will explain the legal basis which allows it to do this. Please note that PIJFC may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, where this is required or permitted by law.PIJFC will use your personal data to carry out its contractual obligations and, in addition, to keep you up-to-date with its products and services that you have expressed an interest in. Where PIJFC act as the data controller for member contact information, it has set out below in the table a description of all the ways it plans to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases PIJFC relies on to do so. PIJFC has also identified what its legitimate interests are, where appropriate.Note that PIJFC may process your personal data for more than one lawful grounds depending on the specific purpose for which PIJFC is using your data. Please contact PIJFC if you need details about the specific legal ground that it is relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.
Purpose/Activity
Type of data
Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest
To register you as a new member (or parent/guardian of a member) and verify your identity (where required)
Identity / contact data
Performance of a contract Consent (for use of special categories of data, if applicable)
To process and deliver the Services including:(a) Manage accounts, payments, fees and charges(b) Contacting you and corresponding about the Services
Identity / contact data
Performance of a contract Necessary for PIJFC’s legitimate interests (to recover debts due to PIJFC)
To respond to queries and enquiries
Identity / contact data
Legitimate interests
To undertake marketing to you
Identity / contact / preferences data
Legitimate interests
Access to your informationPIJFC will not sell or rent your information to third parties. In addition, PIJFC will not share your information for marketing purposes with third party companies.PIJFC may also transfer your personal data if under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply its terms of use or to protect the rights, property or safety of its members. In such situations, PIJFC requires all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. Third party service providers working on behalf of PIJFCPIJFC may pass your information on to the following third party service providers for specific processing activities:The FA: we share player & parent data with the FA , For more information about how the FA processes data please visit the FA privacy notice.Google: PIJFC uses a third party service, G Suite, from Google, to publish its website and manage ad-hoc email correspondence. For more information about how Google processes data, please visit the Google privacy notice.Google Analytics: When someone visits www.pandifootball.net, PIJFC use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. PIJFC do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the website.This information is only processed in a way that does not identify anyone. PIJFC does not make, and does not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. If PIJFC does want to collect personally identifiable information through its website, PIJFC will be up front about it. PIJFC will make it clear when it collects personal information and will explain what it intend to do with it.Teamer: Some of PIJFC's team managers use a third party service, Teamer, to keep in contact regarding match day and training arrangements. For more information about how Teamer processes data, please visit the Teamer privacy notice.Spond: Some of PIJFC's team managers use a third party service, Spond, to keep in contact regarding match day and training arrangements. For more information about how Spond processes data, please visit the Spond privacy notice.How long we keep your information forWhere PIJFC acts as a data controller, it will not keep your personal information longer than is necessary for the purpose in which it was provided, unless required by law, or for other legitimate reasons that need it to be retained for longer (for example, if necessary for any legal proceedings).Your rightsUnder Data Protection Legislation, you have the following rights in certain circumstances:The right to be informed – this is information on PIJFC’s collection and use of your personal data.The right of access – you have the right to be provided with copies of the personal data of you that PIJFC is processing as well as confirmation of the processing PIJFC is doing. You can do this by sending a “subject access request” to the contact details noted above for PIJFC’s consideration.The right to rectification – if you think the personal data that PIJFC holds on you is wrong, you can inform PIJFC and PIJFC will fix it.The right to erasure (also known as the right to be forgotten) – if you want PIJFC to permanently delete the personal data it holds about you then you can ask PIJFC to do so.The right to restrict processing – if you do not like how PIJFC is using your personal data then you can let PIJFC know and PIJFC will stop processing it in that way.The right to data portability – if you want PIJFC to pass on your personal data to someone else then please let PIJFC know. This transfer should not affect the integrity or otherwise damage your personal data.The right to withdraw your consent – you can withdraw your consent for PIJFC to process your personal data (if PIJFC has relied on your consent to process your personal data) at any time by contacting PIJFC. If PIJFC has relied only on your consent as the basis to process your personal data then PIJFC will stop processing your personal data at the point you withdraw your consent. Please note that if PIJFC can also rely on other bases to process your personal data aside from consent then PIJFC may do so even if you have withdrawn your consent.Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling – if PIJFC use either automated decision making or profiling then you have a right to know. Also, PIJFC needs your consent if either of these are used to make a decision that affects you. As with all consent, you can withdraw it at any time.To exercise any of the above rights please email your request to: secretary@pandifootball.net.Where you exercise your right to erasure or where information is deleted in accordance with PIJFC’s retention policy, please note that after the deletion of your personal data, it cannot be recovered, so if you require a copy of this personal data, please request this during the period PIJFC retains the data.Where you exercise your right to request access to the information PIJFC processes about you, you will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, PIJFC may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive.Alternatively, PIJFC may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.PIJFC will try to respond to all legitimate access requests within one month. Occasionally it may take longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, PIJFC will notify you and keep you updated.Links to other websitesFrom time to time, the PIJFC website may contain links to other websites. If you follow a link to another website, please note that the website will have its own privacy policy and that PIJFC does not accept any responsibility or liability for such policies, or how such websites collect and use your data. Please check the associated privacy policy before you submit any personal data to these websites.How to raise a concern about the use of your personal informationIf you have concerns about how we have handled your personal information, including in relation to any of the rights contained herein, please send an email to secretary@pandifootball.net
outlining the concerns that you have.If you are not satisfied with how your complaint has been handled, you can complain to the ICO. You can find further information about the ICO and their complaints procedure at: https://ico.org.uk/concerns/.
FA Charter StandardCharter StandardAnti-discrimination and equal opportunitiesChild Welfare Club ConstitutionCodes of Conduct
ClubContactsDirectionsDevelopmentPrivacy Notice Cookie Policy
Follow us
Share by:
